

BORAN

Computer Engineer



esadboran.github.io

PROFILE

I am a 4th year Computer Engineering student at Hacettepe University. I am constantly improving myself, especially in the fields of Data structures and Artificial Intelligence. I learn programming languages such as Python, Java and C++ in detail and develop small projects using these languages. I think that I have the ability to work and research on any subject.

CONTACT

0 553 463 91 19

esatsuphi@gmail.com

<u>linkedin/esadboran2018</u>

github/esadboran

<u>ANKARA - İZMİR</u>

LANGUAGES

- Turkish(Native Language)
- English (B2 Level)
- German (A1 Level)

EDUCATION

HACETTEPE UNIVERSITY (2018 - 2024)

Computer Science - 3. Year

• GPA: 3.14 / 4

SUPHİ KOYUNCUOĞLU ANATOLIAN HIGH SCHOOL (2014 - 2018)

• GPA: 89.27 / 100

WORK EXPERIENCE

ODAKGIS | September 2018 - December 2018 Volunteer Internship

- Linux learning experience with an Information Security Specialist
- Having good experiences with Computer Engineer software developer working in Python and Java languages

SISBIM June 2022 - July 2022 Internship

- I learned Html, Css, Javascript for web programming
- I developed cloned **Django** projects such as Netflix, Blog, Instagram, and then we created web pages with the team I was with, and we also fixed the errors in our webpage.

SKILL

- Languages: Python, Java, C++,C#, SQL, C
- Knowledge: Machine Learning, Deep Learning, TensorFlow, PyTorch, Computer Vision
- Web: Django, Spring, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React
- Data Analysis, Data Structures, Object Orented Design, Algorithm, Latex, Git
- · Microsoft: Word, Excel, Powerpoint

CERTIFICATE

<u>Improving Deep Neural Networks: Hyperparameter</u> **Tuning, Regularization and Optimization**

June 2023

Türk Telekom & TRAI Veri Bilimi Analitiği Practicum

January 2023

INTRODUCTION TO TENSORFLOW FOR ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE, MACHINE LEARNING, AND DEEP LEARNING

July 2022

PROGRAMMING FOR EVERYBODY (GETTING STARTED **WITH PYTHON)**

February 2022

(40+ HOURS) PYTHON | ADVANCED PROGRAMMING **FROM ZERO**

2021-2022

(40+ HOURS) COMPLETE JAVA DEVELOPER COURSE **FROM ZERO**

2022

HACKKERRANK BASIC PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

2022